### Contact

kocarrasco@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karen-ortiz-carrasco-54b94a19a (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

**Customer Service** 

Communication

Compassion

## Languages

English (Full Professional)

Spanish (Full Professional)

### Certifications

National Registered Paramedic (NRP)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Registered Nurse

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

#### Honors-Awards

Summa Cum Laude

Dean's List Recipient

# Karen Ortiz Carrasco

## Registered Nurse

Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

# Summary

Dedicated, hardworking, and empathetic Registered Nurse. In addition to utilizing my professional experience, education, and passion for serving my community, I provide personalized safe, high-quality care and promote the physical and emotional needs of all patients whom I will interact with.

# Experience

JOHN F KENNEDY MEMORIAL HOSPITAL

Registered Nurse

May 2020 - Present (4 months)

Indio, California, United States

Medical Surgical/COVID-19 RN

Victor Valley Global Medical Center

Registered Nurse

April 2020 - Present (5 months)

Nursery/Postpartum RN

### Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2017 - 2020)

Mt. San Antonio College

Associate of Arts and Sciences - AAS, Social and Behavioral

Science · (2013 - 2019)